ccri.edu 2016-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Web Services - Information Technology - Community College of Rhode Island

The policy of the Community College of Rhode Island is to respect the privacy of all website visitors. We provide this notice to better protect your privacy by explaining our online information practices. This notice applies to all information collected on the CCRI website ([www.ccri.edu](http://www.ccri.edu/)).

##### Information provided voluntarily by you

While using this website, you may choose to supply us with personally identifiable information that is necessary for us to provide you a service or benefit. We will not sell, exchange or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required by law.

##### Network logs and cookies

Information about your website visit may be logged in the course of ensuring network security and to help manage and improve web services. This information could include your IP address, pages visited on the site, and the date and time of the visit. This information is not personally identifiable and we make no attempt to identify individual users from this information. We may use the information to help diagnose technical problems or to provide aggregated statistics. It will not be released to external entities unless we are required by law to do so.

This site may use cookies (which is information stored on your computer by your browser) to maintain data about your current session as you move between pages on the website or to identify you to the site between visits. You may choose through your browser options not to store cookies, however some web pages may not function appropriately. We do not store this information on our computers and do not forward them to external entities.

If you have questions about this site, the collection of personal information, or our online privacy policy, you may contact [webservices@ccri.edu](mailto:webservices@ccri.edu?subject=Web_site_policies "email to webservices").
